umidigi.com 2018-06-23

# UMIDIGI Smartphone

Privacy Policy

UMIDIGI is committed to protecting the privacy of our users. We do not use, store or disclose your information in ways other than those outlined in this Privacy Policy. To better serve you, we may collect information that can be used to identify you. We will not use that information in ways other than laid out in this document. UMIDIGI reserves the right to change or modify this document at any time. Please let us know if you have any questions.

The information we collect and how it is used

In order to better serve you, we collect both personal and non-personal information. The information we collect may include your name, email address, postal address and phone number. Your information may be used in the following ways: When you visit our website, your IP address' geolocation data is used to present you with the most relevant currency and shipping options.  
When you subscribe to the UMIDIGI newsletter, we collect your email to send you news and promotions.  
When you create a UMIDIGI Account, we collect your name and email to validate your account and send you notifications.  
When you participate in our promotions or order products from the UMIDIGI website, we collect your postal address and telephone number for logistical purposes.  
When we ship your order, your postal address will be given to our logistics partners to facilitate delivery.

Managing your personal information

We may occasionally send you news on our products and promotions. If you wish to unsubscribe you may do so in your UMIDIGI Account. You may also modify your information by updating your profile or by sending us a request at   http://umidigi.com/page-contact.html   number for logistical purposes.  
When we ship your order, your postal address will be given to our logistics partners to facilitate delivery.

Disclosure to third parties

We share relevant information with various third-party businesses so that they may provide us with services such as email, website analytics, targeted promotions, payment processing, order processing and delivery. Third party partners are also obligated to protect your privacy and never receive your full account information.In order to optimize your user experience, UMIDIGI uses third-party service providers that offer certain analytics and user interaction services in connection with our website. These services include the collection and tracking of certain data and information regarding the characteristics and activities of visitors to this site. We may disclose Visitor data, including Personally Identifiable Information, to certain such providers in order to obtain these services.Third-party service providers include, but are not limited to, Google Analytics, Kissmetrics, and Optimizely. Kissmetrics' full Privacy Policy can be found here. Visitors may opt out of such analytic and user interaction services via Kissmetrics' Opt-Out Feature, the Opt Out of Optimizely Tracking page, and the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on.

Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of data sent from web servers that are stored on your device. We use cookies to remember user preferences, discover what content is most useful, and facilitate online shopping. We support the Do Not Track browser setting in accordance with the Do Not Track Policy for California. Do Not Track (or DNT) is a preference you can set in your browser to let the websites you visit know that you do not want them collecting certain information about you. For more details about Do Not Track, including how to enable or disable this preference, visit this Do Not Track webpage.

Children's privacy

UMIDIGI takes particular care to protect the safety and privacy of children using our products. In accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we do not knowingly collect information from children under 13. If we have inadvertently collected information of a child under the age of 13 without first obtaining parental consent, we will make effort to immediately delete the information.In accordance with California S.B. 568,"Privacy Rights for California Minors in a Digital World",minors in California may request removal of postings that they have made in the UMIDIGI Forums through their UMIDIGI Accounts.

Location-based Services

In order to better provide recommendations, navigation, weather and other related services, UMIDIGI may collect, use and share with partners relevant information regarding the real-time location of your UMIDIGI device or online login. This information will be collected anonymously.

Third Party Policies

UMIDIGI website and devices may contain links and services offered by third parties. Information collected by such third parties is governed by their own privacy and legal policies.

Commitment to Privacy

At UMIDIGI, we take your privacy very seriously. If you have any questions regarding privacy or would like to make a complaint regarding a privacy breach, please feel free to contact us. We may periodically update our Privacy Policy. When we update our Privacy Policy, we will post the most recent date on which the policy was updated.

UMi (HongKong) Technology Co., Ltd., 

406-407 Jinqi Zhigu Building , 4/F , 1 Tangling Road , Nanshan District 

Shenzhen City, P.R.C

Terms and Conditions

Website terms of service These Terms of Service apply to the website and all subdomains of umidigi.com. All content on this site, including but not limited to text, images, code, design and layout, is owned and controlled by UMIDIGI. No part of the site and content may be reproduced, republished or distributed without the express permission of UMIDIGI. Our services are provided on an as-is and as-available basis, without warranty. We reserve the right to modify these terms and terminate our services at any time. By using this website, you agree to the terms laid out in this document.

Usage of the site

You grant UMIDIGI the right to use, reproduce, modify, and distribute any non-personal, non-confidential content you post. You may not post unlawful, inflammatory, obscene, or otherwise threatening content to our site. Any such content will be deleted and the associated accounts suspended. You may not access unauthorized parts of the site or use the site in any way that will disrupt our services

Changes

We reserve the right to update this document at any time without prior notification. This document was last updated on 18/05/2018.
